let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "question": "8 × 10",
    "answer": 80,
    "options": [
      5,
      28,
      80,
      77
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "question": "5 × 8",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      21,
      36,
      5,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "question": "9 × 7",
    "answer": 63,
    "options": [
      64,
      63,
      1,
      23
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "question": "6 × 7",
    "answer": 42,
    "options": [
      6,
      20,
      40,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "question": "4 × 10",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      24,
      2,
      33,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "question": "0 × 6",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      7,
      10,
      0,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "question": "8 × 1",
    "answer": 8,
    "options": [
      8,
      3,
      14,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "question": "4 × 4",
    "answer": 16,
    "options": [
      4,
      12,
      15,
      16
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "question": "4 × 1",
    "answer": 4,
    "options": [
      3,
      8,
      6,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "question": "4 × 3",
    "answer": 12,
    "options": [
      5,
      12,
      14,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "question": "1 × 10",
    "answer": 10,
    "options": [
      21,
      0,
      7,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 12,
    "question": "1 × 5",
    "answer": 5,
    "options": [
      11,
      5,
      0,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 13,
    "question": "9 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      1,
      0,
      8,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 14,
    "question": "10 × 4",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      40,
      18,
      45,
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 15,
    "question": "6 × 10",
    "answer": 60,
    "options": [
      55,
      7,
      60,
      26
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 16,
    "question": "4 × 5",
    "answer": 20,
    "options": [
      20,
      18,
      14,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 17,
    "question": "2 × 2",
    "answer": 4,
    "options": [
      4,
      5,
      6,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 18,
    "question": "5 × 5",
    "answer": 25,
    "options": [
      25,
      15,
      2,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 19,
    "question": "7 × 5",
    "answer": 35,
    "options": [
      35,
      5,
      36,
      17
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 20,
    "question": "8 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      1,
      8,
      7,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 21,
    "question": "0 × 3",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      0,
      1,
      4,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 22,
    "question": "4 × 5",
    "answer": 20,
    "options": [
      20,
      14,
      10,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 23,
    "question": "6 × 8",
    "answer": 48,
    "options": [
      45,
      22,
      3,
      48
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 24,
    "question": "0 × 3",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      6,
      4,
      8,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 25,
    "question": "3 × 3",
    "answer": 9,
    "options": [
      9,
      8,
      11,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 26,
    "question": "10 × 1",
    "answer": 10,
    "options": [
      12,
      11,
      10,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 27,
    "question": "0 × 9",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      0,
      18,
      10,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 28,
    "question": "0 × 1",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      4,
      2,
      0,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 29,
    "question": "0 × 9",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      2,
      18,
      10,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 30,
    "question": "3 × 6",
    "answer": 18,
    "options": [
      14,
      15,
      1,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 31,
    "question": "5 × 2",
    "answer": 10,
    "options": [
      10,
      9,
      12,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 32,
    "question": "3 × 7",
    "answer": 21,
    "options": [
      17,
      4,
      16,
      21
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 33,
    "question": "8 × 5",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      2,
      18,
      42,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 34,
    "question": "7 × 10",
    "answer": 70,
    "options": [
      6,
      70,
      27,
      66
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 35,
    "question": "6 × 7",
    "answer": 42,
    "options": [
      20,
      5,
      40,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 36,
    "question": "7 × 10",
    "answer": 70,
    "options": [
      66,
      27,
      70,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 37,
    "question": "10 × 10",
    "answer": 100,
    "options": [
      30,
      100,
      2,
      99
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 38,
    "question": "2 × 7",
    "answer": 14,
    "options": [
      16,
      8,
      3,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 39,
    "question": "2 × 9",
    "answer": 18,
    "options": [
      4,
      20,
      10,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 40,
    "question": "5 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      0,
      5,
      1,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 41,
    "question": "4 × 10",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      33,
      2,
      40,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 42,
    "question": "9 × 3",
    "answer": 27,
    "options": [
      15,
      32,
      27,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 43,
    "question": "3 × 7",
    "answer": 21,
    "options": [
      10,
      21,
      16,
      17
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 44,
    "question": "8 × 5",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      18,
      1,
      42,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 45,
    "question": "2 × 10",
    "answer": 20,
    "options": [
      20,
      11,
      22,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 46,
    "question": "8 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      7,
      2,
      8,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 47,
    "question": "6 × 9",
    "answer": 54,
    "options": [
      50,
      24,
      54,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 48,
    "question": "8 × 6",
    "answer": 48,
    "options": [
      49,
      1,
      20,
      48
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 49,
    "question": "2 × 2",
    "answer": 4,
    "options": [
      1,
      3,
      4,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 50,
    "question": "0 × 4",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      10,
      0,
      8,
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 51,
    "question": "4 × 4",
    "answer": 16,
    "options": [
      5,
      12,
      16,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 52,
    "question": "3 × 5",
    "answer": 15,
    "options": [
      8,
      13,
      12,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 53,
    "question": "0 × 9",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      10,
      0,
      18,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 54,
    "question": "3 × 7",
    "answer": 21,
    "options": [
      17,
      21,
      16,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 55,
    "question": "1 × 9",
    "answer": 9,
    "options": [
      9,
      0,
      12,
      19
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 56,
    "question": "6 × 3",
    "answer": 18,
    "options": [
      20,
      18,
      12,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 57,
    "question": "1 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      2,
      3,
      1,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 58,
    "question": "2 × 5",
    "answer": 10,
    "options": [
      12,
      10,
      0,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 59,
    "question": "8 × 2",
    "answer": 16,
    "options": [
      21,
      16,
      0,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 60,
    "question": "2 × 7",
    "answer": 14,
    "options": [
      8,
      16,
      14,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 61,
    "question": "5 × 5",
    "answer": 25,
    "options": [
      7,
      15,
      24,
      25
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 62,
    "question": "1 × 8",
    "answer": 8,
    "options": [
      17,
      5,
      8,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 63,
    "question": "1 × 1",
    "answer": 1,
    "options": [
      3,
      0,
      11,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 64,
    "question": "9 × 8",
    "answer": 72,
    "options": [
      72,
      25,
      2,
      74
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 65,
    "question": "0 × 8",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      2,
      0,
      9,
      16
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 66,
    "question": "8 × 1",
    "answer": 8,
    "options": [
      10,
      8,
      3,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 67,
    "question": "6 × 6",
    "answer": 36,
    "options": [
      36,
      18,
      35,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 68,
    "question": "8 × 7",
    "answer": 56,
    "options": [
      4,
      56,
      22,
      58
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 69,
    "question": "0 × 10",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      12,
      0,
      11,
      20
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 70,
    "question": "5 × 8",
    "answer": 40,
    "options": [
      36,
      6,
      21,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 71,
    "question": "8 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      5,
      7,
      8,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 72,
    "question": "2 × 1",
    "answer": 2,
    "options": [
      4,
      6,
      5,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 73,
    "question": "1 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      2,
      1,
      0,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 74,
    "question": "0 × 5",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      8,
      6,
      0,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 75,
    "question": "0 × 3",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      0,
      14,
      6,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 76,
    "question": "8 × 4",
    "answer": 32,
    "options": [
      16,
      35,
      32,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 77,
    "question": "6 × 5",
    "answer": 30,
    "options": [
      16,
      7,
      30,
      32
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 78,
    "question": "8 × 3",
    "answer": 24,
    "options": [
      28,
      24,
      14,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 79,
    "question": "7 × 5",
    "answer": 35,
    "options": [
      17,
      36,
      3,
      35
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 80,
    "question": "4 × 6",
    "answer": 24,
    "options": [
      16,
      1,
      24,
      21
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 81,
    "question": "0 × 6",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      7,
      14,
      0,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 82,
    "question": "1 × 10",
    "answer": 10,
    "options": [
      10,
      0,
      21,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 83,
    "question": "3 × 10",
    "answer": 30,
    "options": [
      30,
      23,
      8,
      22
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 84,
    "question": "0 × 10",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      7,
      20,
      0,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 85,
    "question": "6 × 3",
    "answer": 18,
    "options": [
      2,
      18,
      12,
      20
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 86,
    "question": "6 × 9",
    "answer": 54,
    "options": [
      4,
      54,
      50,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 87,
    "question": "6 × 10",
    "answer": 60,
    "options": [
      55,
      6,
      60,
      26
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 88,
    "question": "3 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      2,
      5,
      3,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 89,
    "question": "1 × 7",
    "answer": 7,
    "options": [
      13,
      0,
      7,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 90,
    "question": "0 × 2",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      4,
      10,
      0,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 91,
    "question": "7 × 2",
    "answer": 14,
    "options": [
      18,
      11,
      4,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 92,
    "question": "1 × 5",
    "answer": 5,
    "options": [
      5,
      4,
      11,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 93,
    "question": "6 × 3",
    "answer": 18,
    "options": [
      20,
      18,
      3,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 94,
    "question": "5 × 3",
    "answer": 15,
    "options": [
      16,
      15,
      2,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 95,
    "question": "9 × 9",
    "answer": 81,
    "options": [
      27,
      81,
      8,
      80
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 96,
    "question": "2 × 1",
    "answer": 2,
    "options": [
      4,
      11,
      6,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 97,
    "question": "8 × 4",
    "answer": 32,
    "options": [
      1,
      35,
      16,
      32
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 98,
    "question": "2 × 7",
    "answer": 14,
    "options": [
      14,
      7,
      8,
      16
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 99,
    "question": "2 × 6",
    "answer": 12,
    "options": [
      5,
      14,
      7,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 100,
    "question": "4 × 0",
    "answer": 0,
    "options": [
      0,
      4,
      3,
      6
    ]
  }
]